{
    "subject": "resource/WPKN",
    "predicate": "property/airdate",
    "object": "1963",
    "human_readable": "WPKN started airing in 1963.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7480812668800354,
            "question": "What year was the start of WPKN's airtime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7159663438796997,
            "question": "In what decade did WPKN first air?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6464967131614685,
            "question": "When did WPKN begin broadcasting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35819941759109497,
            "question": "Where is WPKN located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30229461193084717,
            "question": "How long has WPKN been broadcasting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2295290231704712,
            "question": "Is WPKN still broadcasting today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22279034554958344,
            "question": "Does WPKN have a website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2099977731704712,
            "question": "Is WPKN a newer or older radio station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19821135699748993,
            "question": "What type of radio station is WPKN?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1428585648536682,
            "question": "What kind of programming does WPKN offer?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WPKN started airing in 1963.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4966_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of radio station is WPKN?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4966_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is WPKN a newer or older radio station?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4966_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does WPKN have a website?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4966_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4966_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4966_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4966_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4966_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4966_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4966_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4966_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4966_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4966_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4966_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that WPKN, the radio station, was founded in 1963 and began broadcasting as a college radio station of the University of Bridgeport. Therefore, the statement \"WPKN started airing in 1963\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}